A Guide to the L. Jane Hastings Architectural Papers, 1951-1998, n.d.
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series III: Project Records, 1959-1998, n.d.
  - Summary of Project Records
    - Kitchell, Frank, alterations ( 1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - B. Kline Residence ( Seattle, WA; 1975; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 12, Box 6, Oversize 11)
    - Klinkam Residence, alterations ( 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Kohler Bathroom, color coordinate program ( Kohler, WI; 1986; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 11)
    - Lackman Residence, addition and remodeling ( Seattle, WA; 1979; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 12)
    - Lake Forest Park Presbyterian Church, remodeling ( 1979; religious ) [Dr] (Oversize 12)
    - Lancaster Residence, new roof addition ( Edmonds, WA; 1991; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 12)
    - Landau, Barbara, remodeling ( Seattle, WA; 1973; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 12)
    - Landau, Barbara, addition ( 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 12)
    - Legge, Mr. and Mrs. Keith, kitchen remodeling ( 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 12)
    - Legge, K.E., summer residence family ( Redondo Beach, WA; 1969; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 12)
    - Legge, Mr. and Mrs. Keith, remodeling ( 1972; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 12)
    - Legge, Mr. and Mrs. Keith, a new garage ( Redondo Beach, WA; 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 12)
    - Leistikow, Mr. and Mrs. Ralph ( Issaquah, WA; 1962; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 13)
    - Leistikow, Mr. and Mrs. Vern ( Issaquah, WA; 1960; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lemme, Mr. and Mrs., new residence ( 1980; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lenzi Residence, deck addition ( 1972; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lewis, Mrs. M., kitchen alterations ( 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lewis, Mr. and Mrs. Ward, alterations ( Hansville, WA; 1985; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lien Residence, remodel ( 1982; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lindsey, Mr. and Mrs., garage ( 1979; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Locks, Vera, addition and remodeling ( Bellevue, WA; 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Loosmore Residence, addition and remodeling ( Bellevue, WA; 1980; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lucks, William G., addition ( 1968; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lucks Residence, alterations ( residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lunneborg, Proposed Terraced Housing - 8 Units ( 1984; residential-multi ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Lurie, H. J., addition and alterations ( 1970; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 13)
    - Madsen Residence, addition and remodeling ( Sumner, WA; 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - Mar-Mic Construction, 15 Unit Apartment ( Bothell, WA; 1967; residential-multi ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - Marriott, Mr. and Mrs. David, alterations ( 1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - Marston, Mr. and Mrs. Daniel J., remodeling ( 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - Martin, Keith, deck addition ( 1967; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - Martin, K. L., addition and alterations ( 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - Maston Residence, alterations ( The Highlands, WA; 1988; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - McAuley, R. B., alterations ( Mercer Island, WA; 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - McAuliffe,Richard, alterations ( 1985; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - McCluskey Residence, addition and remodeling ( 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - McGroskey, Mr. and Mrs. R. D., remodeling ( 1960; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - The McKee Residence ( Bellevue, WA; 1986; residetnial ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - McKinley Family, Beach House ( Whidbey Island, WA; 1965; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 14)
    - McLean, R. B., addition and alterations ( 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 14)
    - Merritt ( Seattle, WA; residential ) [Sl] (Box 6, Box 2)
    - Miller, Mr. and Mrs. J. remodeled ( 1985; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Moll, Dr. Frederic, alterations ( 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Moll, Dr. and Mrs. Frederic, remodeling ( 1960; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Montgomery, R., alterations ( Bellevue, WA; 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Moody, Mr. and Mrs. A. W. ( Issaquah, WA; 1968; residetnial ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Moses, W., addition and alterations ( 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Myers, Francis - Apartment #300 ( 1998; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Myhre, Mr. and Mrs. Richard J. ( Edmonds, WA; 1974; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Myhre, Richard and Dorothy, retreat ( Blaine, WA; 1980; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 15)
    - Nelson, J., kitchen/entry alterations ( 1990; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - Nelson, R. R., addition ( 1960; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - Nelson, W., addition and alterations ( Kirkland, WA; 1970; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - New residence in an established older neighborhood, n.d. (Oversize 23)
    - Norman Residence, greenhouse and deck Addition ( 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - Norman, Mr. and Mrs. T., proposed alterations for the residence ( Lake Forest Park, WA; 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - Norton, remodeling (1973; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - O'Conner/Parks Residence addition/alterations ( 1992; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - O'Connor Residence addition/alterations ( 1989; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - O'Connor, R. residence Addition/Alteration ( 1993; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - Olson Residence, addition and remodeling ( 1983; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - Ormsby, J. W., alterations ( 1972; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - Oswald, Mr. and Mrs. Terry ( 1974; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 16)
    - Padelford Residence, addition and remodeling ( residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Pande ( Indianola, WA; 1975; residential ) [Sl, PB, Ms] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 17, Oversize 25)
    - Paplow/Parish Residence, addition and remodeling ( Woodinville, WA; 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Parks Residence, kitchen remodeling ( 1980; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Parrish, Mr. and Mrs. H. K., proposed garage and work shop ( 1975/1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Parrish, Mr. and Mrs. H. K., proposed remodel and addition ( 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Pasette, Mr. and Mrs. A., kitchen remodel and deck addition ( Seattle, WA; 1976; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 17)
    - Paul Residence, addition and remodeling ( 1962; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Peden Residence, alterations (1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Post, Mr. and Mrs. Fred W., new residence ( Edmonds, WA; 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Pemberton, Mrs .C.W., kitchen remodeling and deck additions (1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Phares, Mr. and Mrs. Mac. E., proposed remodel ( Bellevue, WA; 1974; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Pomeroy, Mr. and Mrs. Stephen B., addition ( 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Poole, Carol, remodeled residence ( 1985; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Quam, David J. ( Seattle, WA; 1968; residential ) [Sl, PB, Ms] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 17, Oversize 24)
    - Rainbow Metals, a remodeled foundary ( 1983; commerical ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Rainier Northwest Group, alterations to existing retail space ( 1983; commerical ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Rainier Northwest University Associates, alterations to existing warehouse ( commerical ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Reed ( 1984 ) [PB, Ms] (Oversize 17, Oversize 29)
    - Rice ( Whidbey Island, WA; 1970; residential ) [Sl, PB, Ms] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 17, Oversize 26)
    - Rice Residence, kitchen/bath alterations ( 1991; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Riggens, Mr. and Mrs. Robert additions ( Mercer Island, WA; 1978; residetnial ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Riley Jr., Mr. and Mrs. Ed, residential remodel ( 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Rinehart Residence addition/alterations ( 1989/1990; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 17)
    - Remodel and Expansion of Salon 1500 ( 1976; commerical ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Salsbury, A. V., stable ( Edmonds [Woodway], WA; 1965; agriculture ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - W. Sandstrom Residence, addition and remodeling ( 1982; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Scates Residence ( 1986; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Schafer, T. and K., proposed alterations ( Mercer Island, WA; 1985; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Schick Residence, additions and remodeling ( 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Schlenker Residence, addition and remodeling ( Woodway, WA; 1979; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Schroeder ( Seattle, WA; 1969; residential ) [Sl, PB, Ms] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 18, Oversize 27)
    - Segale, Mr. and Mrs. Anne ( 1965; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Segale, Ann, new residence ( 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Simons, Dr. E., kitchen alterations ( Edmonds, WA; 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Sirkin/Tripp Residence, addition/alterations ( 1990; 1993; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Smith, Gretchen and Henry, addition ( 1976; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Smith, James, alterations ( 1967; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Soderland, Stanley, addition ( 1963; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Sparling, George, family room addition ( 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 18)
    - Stappler, Mr. Robert, garden and gate roofs ( 1965; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Stearns, Roy and Michael Oller, ski cabin ( Alptental, WA; 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Stevens [Dash Point] ( Tacoma, WA; 1973; residential ) [PB, Ms] (Oversize 19, Oversize 28)
    - Stevens Residence, addition and remodeling ( Bothell, WA; 1981; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Stoner, George H., remodeling ( Mercer Island, WA; 1959; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Strong Residence, addition and remodeling ( 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Strong, a new residence ( Shorewood Hills, WA; 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Sutherland, Mr. and Mrs. David, porch remodeling and deck addition ( 1976; residetnial ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Sutherland, Mr. and Mrs. G. ( 1963; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Symonds Residence, addition and remodeling ( 1982; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 19)
    - Tall Residence, addition and remodeling ( Mercer Island, WA; 1983; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 20)
    - Trolson, Mr. and Mrs. Roy, remodeling ( 1964; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 20)
    - Thompson Residence ( 1987; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 20)
    - Thompson, Terry, addition and remodeling ( Seattle, WA; 1961; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 13, Box 6, Oversize 20)
    - Tulalip Tribes Indian Agency Office, a historical restoration ( Marysville, WA; 1976; government ) [Dr] (Oversize 20)
    - Turnure Residence, alterations ( 1986; residetnial ) [Dr] (Oversize 20)
    - University of Washington, Johnston Hall - Annex "B;" Cunningham Hall ( Seattle, WA; 1980; educational ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 2, Box 6, Oversize 20)
    - Veldee, Mr. and Mrs. Roy ( Mercer Island, WA; 1976; residential ) [Dr, Sl] (Box 6, Box 2, Oversize 20)
    - Vogel, Jessie Residence ( Tacoma, WA; 1981; residential ) [Dr, Ph] (Box 2, Folder 14, Oversize 20)
    - Upper Residence, remodel ( residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 21)
    - Way, Mr. and Mrs. E., alterations ( 1966; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 21)
    - Wimbush, Mr. and Mrs. John A., alterations ( 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 21)
    - Winslow Wright Apartment # 601 ( 1996; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 21)
    - Untitled Project, undated [Dr] (Oversize 21)
    - Youell, Mr. and Mrs. A., summer house ( Hartstene Island, WA; 1982; residential ) [Dr, Ph, Sl] (Box 2, Folder 15, Box 6, Oversize 21)
    - Young, Mr. and Mrs. James C., new residence ( 1978; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 21)
    - Young Residence ( Kent, WA; 1984; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 21)
    - Zaremba,Dr. and Mrs. A.M., garage addition ( Monroe, WA; 1969; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 21)
    - Zebelman Residence, addition/alterations ( 1988; residential ) [Dr] (Oversize 21)
- Series IV: Art and Artifacts, 1952-1989, Box 7 includes 2 registration stamps, a set of drafting tools, a set of lettering tools, and a miniature book by one of Hastings' clients featuring Hastings' Reed House. Box 8 includes four commemorative UIFA scarves, including a furoshiki cloth designed by Keizuke Serizawa for UIFA 1998 (Japan), a silk scarf designed for UIFA 1983 (Paris, France), a silk scarf designed for UIFA 1976 (Iran), and a silk scarf designed for an unknown UIFA event. (Box 7, Box 8)